muzu.tv 2013-06-04

# Privacy Policy

**1.      ****WHO WE ARE AND WHAT THIS POLICY IS FOR...**

1.1.   Our name is Our Digital Universe Limited and we operate MUZU™ TV ("Our Website") for your enjoyment. If you need to contact us for any reason then all correspondence should be sent to the General Manager at our address is 19 South William Street, Dublin 2, Ireland (Company No. 402870).

1.2.   We want you to trust us and use Our Website safe in the knowledge that we will not use any information you give us in any way that you are not comfortable with or have not agreed to. In this policy we have set out in clear and easily understandable language how and for what purposes we will use information you provide us with.

1.3.   Registering as a "Member" is free and a strictly voluntary process. You do get some cool information and access to great features on Our Website if you do register, but membership is not necessary to simply visit Our Website and browse what is available on it.

**2.      ****YOUR INFO...**

2.1.   We collect and maintain personally identifiable information ("Your Info") that you provide to us. This includes your name, an email address, and a password as part of your Member profile. We may supplement this information with information we receive about you from our commercial partners, but this information will be dealt with in the same way and receive the same security as any of Your Info provided directly to us.

2.2.   Our software uses Your Info to personalise and manage Our Website for you. For example, Our Website stores your favourite Artist Channels and music preferences. If you do decide to give us any of Your Info, you are telling us that this information is both true and accurate. Also, you are telling us that you are entitled to provide us with that information.

2.3.   We will always comply with the Data Protection Act 1998 and all other applicable laws relevant to our handling Your Info.

2.4.   In order to make our site more efficient, we may also collect certain non-personal information (such as site usage behaviour) based on your use of Our Website. We may use this information to display advertising that we think you will find interesting and suppress advertising that you might find boring or annoying.

2.5.   To help us debug problems with our software (rare as they are), we may collect some technical information from your browser software (such as Mozilla Firefox or Internet Explorer), screen resolution and the website that referred you to us.

**3.      ****WE'LL KEEP YOU INFORMED...**

3.1.   When you choose to register with us and become a Member, you will need to provide us with your email address.

3.2.   Providing us with your email address gives us the chance to email you a new password in case you forget or lose your old one. This is normal and happens to the best of us, particularly those of us that are incredibly busy. If you do register with us, Our Website will save your information and recognise you regardless of where you login from, so if you are visiting friends and using their computer, we'll know it's you and display your searches and preferences when you do login with your personal email address and password.

3.3.   At the time of registering to become a Member we give you the option of receiving emails from us. We think they are quite amusing, useful and contain the sort of information about Our Website and your favourite artists that you would like to receive but you may not and can opt out any time. Our emails are sent from a MUZU™ TV address and are sent to your real email address. Every email that we send has an opt-out URL, so you can unsubscribe when you want.

**4.      ****WHAT WE'LL DO WITH YOUR INFO...**

4.1.   What's yours is yours. Any of Your Info that you chose to share with us stays with us and our record labels and musician partners (the "Music Guys"). We won't sell Your Info to anyone and only us and the Music Guys will have access to it. There might be one exception in the event Our Website itself is sold. In this case we would transfer Your Info to our buyers so that they could continue to provide the same great MUZU™ TV service.

4.2.   We may also use Your Info:

4.2.1.  to help us decide what products and services would be of most interest to you;

4.2.2.  to understand your preferences so we can improve the service and facilities offered by Our Website;

4.2.3.  for record keeping purposes;

4.2.4.  for market research;

4.2.5.  to track activity on and from Our Website;

4.2.6.  to provide you with information on products and services which we may think would be of interest to you, but only where you have specifically consented to us contacting you for this purpose;

4.3.   We occasionally will share aggregated usage information with others. This type of information does not contain your identity or anything personally identifiable to you.

**5.      ****IF THE AUTHORITIES COME KNOCKING...**

5.1.   We may disclose Your Info to properly authorised third parties to whom we are required to disclose such information by law. This might include disclosing Your Info where we reasonably believe that you are attempting to commit fraud, conduct activities that could bring harm to others, are using Our Website for any other criminal or immoral purpose or are in serious breach of the [terms and conditions of use](http://www.muzu.tv/site/legal/) of Our Website. If you are using Our Website for reasons other than simply enjoying the Artist channels and innocently interacting with the Music Guys and other users, please don't worry as this section will not affect you.

**6.      ****YOU'RE THE BOSS...**

6.1.   Members of Our Website and site visitors have control over the use of their personal data. Whether or not you have agreed to us using Your Info in a certain way before, you always can change your account settings (and consent or decline to use in the same manner) in the "My Profile" page on Our Website....You call the shots!

**7.      ****HOW WE LOOK AFTER YOUR INFO...**

7.1.   We have a sophisticated security program intended to keep the information stored in our systems protected from unauthorised access. We store Your Info in secure locations in Ireland or other secure locations outside of Ireland where we have systems that are configured with data encryption, or scrambling technologies and firewalls constructed to the highest industry standards. We also use Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology that protects the data you send over the Internet. Third party companies review our internal security policies and documentation regularly.

7.2.   The bottom line is, when it comes to information security, we mean business. Some of the Music Guys may operate in countries such as the United States (or otherwise outside of the EU) so as a result Your Info may therefore be transferred beyond the shores of the EU. Giving any of Your Info to us means you agree your continued use of Our Website is your consent to this transfer.

7.3.   Unfortunately, the transmission of information via the internet or mobile channels is not completely secure. Although we will do our best to protect your private information, we cannot guarantee the security of your data transmitted to our site; any transmission is at your own risk. Once we have received your information, we will use strict procedures and security features to try to prevent unauthorised access

**8.      ****COOKIES (THE NOT SO TASTY VERSIONS)...**

8.1.   When you visit Our Website we may store information about your web session and assign you one or more 'cookies'. Your browser will store these cookies on your computer in a small text file. For example, when you decide to login as a Member, we store encrypted information in your browser so you don't have to login on every page.

8.2.   Permanent cookie files remain on your computer's hard drive until you delete them manually using your browser or operating system software. You can enable your browser to refuse cookies, but doing so may disable access to some services and tools that we offer.

8.3.   In order to offer this service both the Music Guys and ourselves do make money by selling advertising on Our Website and the Artist Channels. Our third party advertising partners often use a cookie or third party web beacon (such as a single pixel GIF image) to track when a click by you on advertising on Our Website becomes a sale. None of Your Info is ever sent to these advertising partners.

8.4.   We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit Our Website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to Our Website and other websites in order to provide advertisements that are more relevant to goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, click here: [networkadvertising.org](http://networkadvertising.org/consumer/opt_out.asp).

8.5.   MUZU.TV partners with third party ad networks and allows such networks to use cookies to collect non-personally identifiable data for targeting and serving ads. Users can opt-out of this behavioral targeting by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative's consumer page at [http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp).

**9.      ****WE DON'T CONTROL THE WHOLE OF THE WORLD WIDE WEB...**

9.1.   Although we only work with responsible third parties, their business policies may include different privacy policies and data-sharing practices to our own. When you click through to third party website from Our Website, please bear in mind that our privacy policies no longer apply. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of all websites you jump to from our own.

**10.    ****TEENAGERS AND ABOVE ONLY PLEASE...**

10.1. In accordance with our [terms and conditions of use](http://www.muzu.tv/site/legal/), we do not knowingly collect personal information from people under the age of 13. If we become aware of the fact that a minor is attempting to submit this information, we will inform the minor that he or she is ineligible to do so. We will then remove this information from our records.

**11.    ****OCCASIONAL CHANGES TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY...**

11.1. We do reserve the right to modify this privacy policy at any time. If there are material changes that significantly affect how we will use Your Info, we will prominently post these changes on Our Website prior to implementing them.

11.2. If you use Our Website after we post these changes to the privacy policy, this indicates your acceptance of them. Regardless of later updates, we will follow the practices described in this privacy policy at the time you provided us with your information. If you ever have questions about our privacy policies, please contact us using the following [link](http://www.muzu.tv/site/contactUs).
